Hello everyone, my name is Darmik Therapada and I made one type of Chrome extension.
We all know that Google is integrated their Germany feature in their almost product.
So and one thing I noticed that in Google Classroom they didn't integrate their Germany
features.
So I made one kind of Chrome extension that self you to understanding your Google Class
room documentation.
You can ask any question about your classroom documentation.
It will help you to answering.
Let me show you.
So all I want to randomly documentation.
Let's ask about our SQL connection class.
You can see that guys.
SQL connection equal to new I-SK1X on.
Head there and data blah blah.
This line of code is creating a new instance of SK1XM class.
We all know that it reply very well.
Let's start.
Try again.
I open a combination logic video and just ask about video random things.
Move prepared this video and explain combination circuit.
I don't know guys.
I don't know like it.
It's almost explained using example and diagram also told that.
Let's try another thing.
I just asked let me know over you of this video.
Right now you can just see that it's tell.
Move prepared this period and it's over you.
That's my chrome plugin.
You can use my given code.